{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Intrinsic semiconductor material is characterized by a valence shell of how many electrons?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "4", "optd": "6", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Ionization within a P-N junction causes a layer on each side of the barrier called the:", "opta": "junction", "optb": "depletion region", "optc": "barrier voltage", "optd": "forward voltage", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the most significant development in electronics since World War II?", "opta": "the development of color TV", "optb": "the development of the diode", "optc": "the development of the transistor", "optd": "the development of the TRIAC", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What causes the depletion region?", "opta": "doping", "optb": "diffusion", "optc": "barrier potential", "optd": "ions", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an energy gap?", "opta": "the space between two orbital shells", "optb": "the energy equal to the energy acquired by an electron passing a 1 V electric field", "optc": "the energy band in which electrons can move freely", "optd": "an energy level at which an electron can exist", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Silicon atoms combine into an orderly pattern called a:", "opta": "covalent bond", "optb": "crystal", "optc": "semiconductor", "optd": "valence orbit", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In \"n\" type material, majority carriers would be:", "opta": "holes", "optb": "dopants", "optc": "slower", "optd": "electrons", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Elements with 1, 2, or 3 valence electrons usually make excellent:", "opta": "conductors", "optb": "semiconductors", "optc": "insulators", "optd": "neutral", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A commonly used pentavalent material is:", "opta": "arsenic", "optb": "boron", "optc": "gallium", "optd": "neon", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which material may also be considered a semiconductor element?", "opta": "carbon", "optb": "ceramic", "optc": "mica", "optd": "argon", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In \"p\" type material, minority carriers would be:", "opta": "holes", "optb": "dopants", "optc": "slower", "optd": "electrons", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The purpose of p-type doping is to create an abundance of holes. In the case of silicon, a trivalent atom (typically from Group 13 of the periodic table, such as boron or aluminium) is substituted into the crystal lattice. The result is that one electron is missing from one of the four covalent bonds normal for the silicon lattice. Thus the dopant atom can accept an electron from a neighboring atom's covalent bond to complete the fourth bond. This is why such dopants are called acceptors. The dopant atom accepts an electron, causing the loss of half of one bond from the neighboring atom and resulting in the formation of a \"hole\". Each hole is associated with a nearby negatively charged dopant ion, and the semiconductor remains electrically neutral as a whole. However, once each hole has wandered away into the lattice, one proton in the atom at the hole's location will be \"exposed\" and no longer cancelled by an electron. This atom will have 3 electrons and 1 hole surrounding a particular nucleus with 4 protons. For this reason a hole behaves as a positive charge. When a sufficiently large number of acceptor atoms are added, the holes greatly outnumber thermal excited electrons. Thus, holes are the majority carriers, while electrons become minority carriers in p-type materials."}, {"question": "What can a semiconductor sense?", "opta": "magnetism", "optb": "temperature", "optc": "pressure", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an electron jumps from the valence shell to the conduction band, it leaves a gap. What is this gap called?", "opta": "energy gap", "optb": "hole", "optc": "electron-hole pair", "optd": "recombination", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Forward bias of a silicon P-N junction will produce a barrier voltage of approximately how many volts?", "opta": "0.2", "optb": "0.3", "optc": "0.7", "optd": "0.8", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which semiconductor material is made from coal ash?", "opta": "germanium", "optb": "silicon", "optc": "tin", "optd": "carbon", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When and who discovered that more than one transistor could be constructed on a single piece of semiconductor material:", "opta": "1949, William Schockley", "optb": "1955, Walter Bratten", "optc": "1959, Robert Noyce", "optd": "1960, John Bardeen", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When is a P-N junction formed?", "opta": "in a depletion region", "optb": "in a large reverse biased region", "optc": "the point at which two opposite doped materials come together", "optd": "whenever there is a forward voltage drop", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A P-N junction mimics a closed switch when it:", "opta": "has a low junction resistance", "optb": "is reverse biased", "optc": "cannot overcome its barrier voltage", "optd": "has a wide depletion region", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solid state devices were first manufactured during:", "opta": "World War 2", "optb": "1904", "optc": "1907", "optd": "1960", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Electron pair bonding occurs when atoms:", "opta": "lack electrons", "optb": "share holes", "optc": "lack holes", "optd": "share electrons", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many valence electrons are in every semiconductor material?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is a type of doping material?", "opta": "extrinsic semiconductor material", "optb": "pentavalent material", "optc": "n-type semiconductor", "optd": "majority carriers", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Minority carriers are many times activated by:", "opta": "heat", "optb": "pressure", "optc": "dopants", "optd": "forward bias", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the voltage across R1 if the P-N junction is made of silicon?", "opta": "12 V", "optb": "11.7 V", "optc": "11.3 V", "optd": "0 V", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If conductance increases as temperature increases, this is known as a:", "opta": "positive coefficient", "optb": "negative current flow", "optc": "negative coefficient", "optd": "positive resistance", "ans": "C", "explanation": "A negative temperature coefficient (NTC) occurs when the thermal conductivity of a material rises with increasing temperature, typically in a defined temperature range.\nNote: The reciprocal of electrical Resistance is called Conductance."}, {"question": "Which of the following cannot actually move?", "opta": "majority carriers", "optb": "ions", "optc": "holes", "optd": "free electrons", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What electrical characteristic of intrinsic semiconductor material is controlled by the addition of impurities?", "opta": "conductivity", "optb": "resistance", "optc": "power", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}